http://www.bellevue.edu/footer/privacy/

! For COVID-19 Information ›
Coming to campus? Take the BRUIN Return to Learn Screening first. ›
Login
Need Help?
Center for Natural Science
Bellevue University is accredited by the Higher Learning Commission (hlcommission.org).
Privacy Policy
At Bellevue University, we take your personal privacy seriously. This policy describes the categories of information we gather
via this website, describes how such information may be shared with others, and identifies the categories of persons with whom
it may be shared.
General
This online privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to Bellevue University’s Internet web site located at www.bellevue.edu,
including affiliated web sites owned by Bellevue University which contain authorized links to this policy (collectively, the
“Site” or “Bellevue University Site”). The Site is governed by this Privacy Policy as amended from time to time, and not the
privacy policy in effect at the time any data or information was collected. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information
collected at any site that is not owned by Bellevue University, including any web site reached through a link on any Bellevue
University Site. Please regularly review our Privacy Policy. If you have objections to the Privacy Policy, you should
immediately discontinue use of the Site. This Privacy Policy does not govern privacy practices associated with offline
activities or websites other than the Site. Bellevue University employees, faculty members and students may be subject to
other Bellevue University policies and agreements related to this Privacy Policy or otherwise intended for the protection of
certain personal and confidential information (collectively, the “Bellevue Policies”). You expressly acknowledge that your
obligations and responsibilities under the Bellevue Policies, as applicable, are not superseded by this Privacy Policy and
that the Bellevue Policies shall be used together with this Privacy Policy to protect the personal and confidential information
of Bellevue University and its employees, faculty members and students to the fullest extent allowed by law.
The Site is intended for adult audiences, and Bellevue University does not knowingly collect any information that identifies
or any information that can be used to identify the individual to whom such information pertains (“Personal Information”)
from anyone under thirteen (13) years of age. If you are under thirteen, please do not give us any Personal Information.
If you have reason to believe that a child has provided Personal Information to us, please contact us and we will attempt to
remove that information from our databases.
Changes in Privacy Policy
Any Personal Information that we collect and maintain via the Site will be subject to this Privacy Policy, as amended from
time to time. Bellevue University may change this Privacy Policy from time to time at its sole discretion. If as the result
of such changes you want to alter the ways in which Bellevue University is allowed to use your Personal Information, you can
do so by following the procedure described in the section entitled “Updating Your Personal Information Preferences.” You will
be deemed to have been made aware of, and will be subject to, the changes to this Privacy Policy after such changes have been
posted.
FERPA
Bellevue University is obligated to comply with certain educational records standards pursuant to the Family Educational
Rights and Privacy Act ("FERPA"). To the extent applicable, FERPA, as well as Bellevue University’s FERPA compliance policy,
govern the collection and use of information through the Bellevue University Site. Please note that FERPA is applicable to
information you provide only if you are or become a student of Bellevue University and permits the use, sharing and disclosure
of "Directory Information." For purposes of FERPA and this Privacy Policy, "Directory information" means your name, major
field of study, participation in recognized activities and sports, height and weight of members of athletic teams, dates of
attendance, degree and awards received and most recent previous school attended. If you do not want such information about
you to be disclosed, please contact the Student Records at 1.402.557.7386 or 1.800.756.7920 extension 7386 or by e-mail at Regaddr@bellevue.edu.
You may opt out of disclosure of this information only if you are now or become a student of Bellevue University. Current students at Bellevue
University should refer to the Bellevue University Student Handbook or contact the Student Records, the Director of Student Financial Services
or Enrollment Management to obtain additional information regarding Bellevue University’s compliance with FERPA.
Collection of Personal Information
As a visitor to this Site, you can engage in many activities without providing any Personal Information. However, when you use
the Site, Bellevue University may collect certain information about your computer to facilitate, evaluate and verify your use
of the Site. For example, we may log environmental variables, such as browser type, operating system, CPU speed, referring or
exit webpages, click patterns, Session ID (a unique identifier assigned to the browser in connection to the Site), and the
Internet Protocol (IP) address of your computer. Bellevue University may use such information to measure traffic patterns on
the Site and to improve user and student experiences with the Site.
Except as provided below, we do not match such information
with Personal Information held about you by Bellevue University unless we have your consent.
In order to reduce errors in our
database, prevent fraud and prevent abuse of our Site, as well as to provide more consistent, relevant experiences to our users
and students, we may on occasion supplement or correct the Personal Information you submit to us and your IP address with
information in our other databases.
Any Personal Information collected by Bellevue University via this Site is collected only upon your voluntary submission of
the same. We collect Personal Information that you voluntarily provide to us through the Site when you sign up to receive more
information about our programs or otherwise contact us through the forms available on the Site. We also collect information
during the application and matriculation process, and, if you are enrolled as a student, when providing education to you or
when you use pages of the Site made available to you while you are a student. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information
collected through means other than the Bellevue University Site.
Updating Your Personal Information Preferences
You have the right to access, correct and delete inaccuracies in your Personal Information, or request a change in the way
Bellevue University uses your Personal Information, at any time. You may access and correct your Personal Information or
request such changes by contacting us at Student Records at 1.402.557.7386 or 1.800.756.7920 extension 7386 or by e-mail at
Regaddr@bellevue.edu.
In your correspondence, please indicate with as much detail as possible the location on this Site or otherwise where you
provided your Personal Information. You may expect a response within thirty (30) days.
Sharing Personal Information
Bellevue University recognizes and appreciates the importance of responsible use of the Personal Information collected on the
Site. Bellevue University will respect your legal rights regarding access to, and correction and deletion of, your Personal
Information. However, there are instances in which Bellevue University may divulge your Personal Information, such as when
required by law, regulation, or litigation. We may also disclose information about you if we determine that such disclosure
should be made for reasons of national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. Finally, we may use
and share your Personal Information to:
(1) contact you or enable our authorized contractors to help us contact you; (2)
satisfy our reporting obligations under FERPA or other applicable laws; (3) protect the rights, property or safety of Bellevue
University, students, employees, faculty members, contractors, agents or other users of this site; and (4) enforce Bellevue
University’s Website Terms and Conditions of Use.
By using the Bellevue University Site, you understand and agree that we may use and share the Personal Information that you
provide in these ways.
Communications Venues
During your educational experience at Bellevue University, you may participate in online educational sessions or other
interactive activities, including, but not limited to, online bulletin boards, social networking sites, blogs, Wikis,
calendars, forums and other message or communication facilities designed to enable you to communicate with others
(“Communications Venues”). Please note that any information you disclose in any such Communications Venues,
may be available to other participants and to Bellevue University, its employees, faculty members and contractors and to all
other persons accessing such Communications Venues.
The information you share may be read, collected or used by others for
any purpose, including sending you unsolicited messages. Bellevue University is not responsible for any information you elect
to submit in these Communications Venues or the use of such information. All information presented in Communications Venues
reflects the views of the individual users or instructors and does not necessarily reflect the views of Bellevue University.
Tracking, Use of Cookies and Similar Devices
In order to improve the Site and provide more convenient, relevant experiences to our visitors and students, we and our
agents may use “cookies” and similar devices to track your activities. A cookie is a small amount of data that is transferred
to your browser by a web server and can only be read by the server that gave it to you.
It cannot be executed as code or
deliver viruses. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies.
You can set your browser to notify you when you receive
a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it.
Google Analytics
This website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”,
which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the
cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the
United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website
activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer
this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google‘s
behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using this website, you consent to the
processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this
you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. Furthermore, you can prevent Google’s collection and use of data
(cookies and IP address) by downloading and installing the browser plug-in available from Google at: tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout
Further information about Google Analytics can be found at: support.google.com/analytics/answer/6004245
For more information about deleting and controlling cookies, visit: www.aboutcookies.org
Links to Other Sites
The Site may contain links to other web sites, such as links to online bookstores, educational institutions, and other third
parties that may provide information, services or products to you. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, the
content of, or any other actions of such other web sites or their owners or operators, such as their practices regarding
cookies, information they may collect or information they may share, or whether they may permit advertisers to place and use
cookies. You should review the privacy policies at each of these sites.
Conditions of Use
This Privacy Policy shall be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of Nebraska.
By using our
Site, you consent to the collection and use of information as described above. Your visit and any dispute over privacy are
subject to this Privacy Policy and the Bellevue University Website Terms and Conditions of Use.
Website Terms and Conditions of Use
Please read this document carefully before accessing or using the Internet web site located at www.bellevue.edu, including
affiliated web sites owned by Bellevue University, a Nebraska non-profit corporation (“Bellevue University”) which contain
authorized links to this document (collectively, the “Site” or “Bellevue University Site”).
By accessing or using this Site
in any way, including using any Services (as defined below), downloading Materials (as defined below) or merely browsing the
Site, you agree to and are bound by the terms and conditions set forth in this document and in any changes thereto that
Bellevue University may publish from time to time (collectively, the “Terms of Use”). If you do not agree to all of the terms
and conditions contained in the Terms of Use, do not access or use this Site.
Bellevue University may change the Terms of Use and other guidelines and rules posted on the Site from time to time at its
sole discretion. Your continued access or use of the Site, or any Materials or Services, constitutes your acceptance of the
changes. Your access and use of the Site, Materials and Services will be subject to the most current version of the Terms of
Use posted on the Site at the time of such use. Please regularly check the “Terms of Use” link at http://www.bellevue.edu/footer/privacy/index.aspx to
view the then-current terms.
If you breach any of the Terms of Use, your authorization to access or use this Site, Services
and Materials automatically terminates, and any Materials downloaded or printed from the Site in violation of the Terms of Use
must be immediately destroyed. These Terms of Use are in addition to Bellevue University’s other terms, conditions, policies,
rules and regulations relating to course instruction and other educational programs and opportunities provided by Bellevue
University.
The Site
The Site, including all Materials and Services provided via the Site, are available for your access and use subject to the
Terms of Use. “Materials” means all information, data, documents, communications, downloads, files, text, images, photographs,
graphics, videos, webcasts, publications, content, tools, resources, code, programs and products made available or enabled via
the Site by Bellevue University. “Services” means all services and resources offered or enabled via the Site by Bellevue
University and users of this Site, including download areas, information services and communications services such as online
bulletin boards, social networking sites, blogs, Wikis, calendars, forums and other message or communication facilities
designed to enable you to communicate with others (“Communications Venues”).
Intellectual Property; Trademark Information
The Materials and Services, as well as their selection and arrangement, are protected by copyrights, trademarks, patents,
trade secrets and all other intellectual property and proprietary rights (collectively, “Intellectual Property Rights”), and
any unauthorized use of the Materials or Services may violate such laws and the Terms of Use. Except as expressly provided
herein, Bellevue University does not grant any express or implied rights to use the Materials and Services. You agree not to
copy, republish, frame, download, transmit, modify, adapt, create derivative works based on, rent, lease, loan, sell, assign,
distribute, display, perform, license, sublicense or reverse engineer the Site, Materials or Services, any portions of the
Site, Materials or Services or the selection and arrangement of the Site, Materials or Services, except as expressly authorized
herein. In addition, you agree not to use any data mining, robots or similar data gathering and extraction methods in
connection with the Site, Services or Materials.
The trademarks, service marks, logos, URLs and domain names (“Marks”) displayed on this Site are the property of Bellevue
University. You are not permitted to use the Marks without the prior written consent of Bellevue University.
Use of Site and Services
You shall pay all costs and charges, including phone charges and telecommunications equipment costs, that you incur in order
to access or use the Site, Services and Materials. You must adhere to all limitations on dissemination, usage and reproduction
of any Materials that you download from the Site that are subject to such limitations. You agree to use the Services only to
access, download, utilize, post, send or receive Materials in an appropriate manner as related to the particular Materials or
Services being accessed or used by you.
You are solely responsible for the content of any transmissions you make to the Site
or to any Bellevue University faculty member, employee, contractor, agent or student.
As some examples of improper activities
when accessing or using the Site, Services or Materials, you agree that you shall not:
Promote any unlawful activity or purpose, including without limitation, any activity that could give rise to criminal or civil liability.
Collect, harvest, mine or engage in any other activity to obtain e-mail addresses, phone numbers, personal information or
any other information about Bellevue University employees, faculty members, students, or others.
Use or attempt to gain access to or use another's account, password, Service, Materials or computer systems connected to
any Bellevue University server or to the Site, whether through hacking, password mining or any other means.
Remove or falsely add to any Materials any copyright, trademark or other legal or proprietary rights notices, author
attributions or other information such as origin or source of the Material(s).
Make available any files containing Materials where you do not own or control, or have not received the necessary
licenses to, all Intellectual Property Rights, rights of privacy and publicity and all other rights in and to such
Materials.
Use the Site, Services or any Materials in any manner that infringes any Intellectual Property Rights or other rights of
any party.
Disrupt or interfere with the security of, or otherwise cause harm to, the Site, or any Services, Materials, systems
resources, accounts, passwords, servers or networks connected to or accessible through the Site or any affiliated sites.
Transmit unsolicited or bulk communications to any Bellevue University affiliated e-mail address.
Post or otherwise submit any software, programs or files that are harmful or disruptive of another’s equipment, software
or other property, including any corrupted files, time bombs, Trojan horses, viruses and worms.
Create a false identity for the purpose of misleading others.
Download any Materials posted by another that you know, or reasonably should know, cannot be legally reproduced,
distributed, performed or displayed in such manner.
Disrupt, interfere or inhibit any other user from using and enjoying the Site or other affiliated or Linked Sites,
Materials or Services.
Breach any guidelines, rules, policies or other codes of conduct applicable to your status with Bellevue University and
your activity on the Site, including, but not limited to, the policies provided in the Bellevue University Student
Handbook, the Bellevue University Course Catalog, applicable Bellevue University Employee and/or Faculty Handbooks and
related policy statements (“Bellevue University Policies”).
Access or use the Site in any manner that could damage, disable, overburden or impair any Bellevue University server or
the network(s) connected to any Bellevue University server.
Violate any applicable laws or regulations related to the access to or use of the Site, Services or any Materials or
engage in any activity prohibited by the Terms of Use.
Post or otherwise submit any topic, name, material or information that is child pornography, defamatory, excessively
violent, harassing, inappropriate, indecent, lascivious, lewd, obscene, profane, racist, unlawful, or otherwise
objectionable.
Prepare, compile, use, download or otherwise copy any Site user directory or other user or usage information or any
portion thereof, or transmit, provide or otherwise distribute (whether or not for a fee) such directory or information
to any third party.
Engage in any chain letters, contests, junk e-mail, pyramid schemes, spamming, surveys or any other duplicative or
unsolicited messages (commercial or otherwise).
Violate the rights of Bellevue University or any third party (including rights of privacy and publicity) or abuse,
defame, harass, stalk or threaten another.
Use any Bellevue University domain name as a pseudonymous return e-mail address.
Market any goods or services for any business purpose (including advertising and making offers to buy or sell goods or
services), unless specifically allowed to do so by Bellevue University.
The foregoing list of prohibitions provides examples and is not a complete or exclusive list.
In addition, if you are a
student of Bellevue University or an employee or faculty member of Bellevue University, you have certain responsibilities with
respect to your conduct as set forth in applicable Bellevue University Policies. Your conduct on the Site is subject to and
must fully conform with the Bellevue University Policies. Violation of the Bellevue University Policies (and any other
policies, rules or guidelines that may be applicable) may result in appropriate sanctions, as determined in Bellevue
University’s sole and absolute discretion, in addition to the any other consequence, penalty or liability that may result from
such behavior.
Usage and Monitoring
You may use the Site only as intended by Bellevue University. While Bellevue University has no obligation to monitor the Site
and is not responsible for the content of any messages, information or files transmitted on the Site or via Communications
Venues, Bellevue University reserves the right to delete and take other appropriate action with respect to such messages,
information or files which Bellevue University, in its sole discretion, deems objectionable or otherwise in violation of the
Terms and Conditions, including denying access to the Site to anyone at anytime. All persons are hereby notified that use of
the Site constitutes consent to such actions, monitoring and auditing.
By posting or submitting Materials, you represent and
warrant that you own or otherwise control all of the Intellectual Property Rights and other rights to such Materials as
described in these Terms of Use, including all the rights necessary for you to post or submit such Materials.
You are solely and entirely responsible for all Materials that you post or otherwise submit via the Site or via Communications
Venues. You shall assume all risks associated with the use of such Materials including any reliance on the accuracy,
completeness or usefulness of such Materials. Bellevue University does not guarantee the accuracy, integrity or quality of
these Materials. You acknowledge and agree that by accessing or using the Site or Services, you may be exposed to Materials
from others that are offensive, indecent or otherwise objectionable.
Bellevue University's Rights to Submitted Materials
For all Materials that you post or otherwise submit to the Site, you grant Bellevue University and the users of this Site an
unrestricted, irrevocable, non-exclusive, worldwide, royalty-free and fully paid up license under all Intellectual Property
Rights to use, reproduce, publicly display, publicly perform, copy, edit, modify, translate, reformat, transmit and distribute
such Materials, with or without having your name attached to such Materials, in any manner or form and for any purpose, with
full rights to sublicense such rights through multiple tiers of distribution.
You acknowledge and agree that Bellevue
University shall not be liable for any failure to store such Materials on the Site at any time.
Restriction and Termination of Use
Bellevue University may block, restrict, disable, suspend or terminate your access to all or part of the Site, Services and
Materials at any time in Bellevue University’s sole discretion, without prior notice or liability to you.
Links to Third Party Sites
The Site, Services or Materials may include links that will take you to other sites outside of the Site ("Linked Sites").
For example, there is a link on the Bellevue University Site to an online bookstore owned and operated by Follett Higher
Education Group.
While the name and logo of Bellevue University may appear on this an other Linked Sites, as a way to
conveniently notify students of the sale of certain materials specified for Bellevue University’s curriculum, Bellevue
University does not operate this online bookstore.
This and other Linked Sites are provided by Bellevue University to you as
a convenience and the inclusion of the links does not imply any endorsement by Bellevue University of any Linked Site.
Bellevue University has no control of the Linked Sites and you therefore acknowledge and agree that Bellevue University is
not responsible for the contents of any Linked Site, any link contained in a Linked Site or any changes or updates to a
Linked Site. You further acknowledge and agree that Bellevue University is not responsible for any form of transmission
(e.g. webcasting) received from any Linked Site.
Warranties and Disclaimers
THE SITE, SERVICES AND MATERIALS ARE PROVIDED BY BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY UNDER THESE TERMS OF USE "AS IS" WITHOUT WARRANTY OF ANY
KIND, EITHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, WHETHER BY STATUTE, COMMON LAW, CUSTOM, USAGE OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO,
PERFORMANCE, SECURITY, INTEGRATION, QUIET ENJOYMENT, SATISFACTORY QUALITY, AND THE IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF TITLE,
NON-INFRINGEMENT, MERCHANTABILITY OR FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. WITHOUT LIMITING THE FOREGOING, BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY
MAKES NO WARRANTY THAT (i) THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS WILL MEET YOUR REQUIREMENTS; (ii) THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS
WILL BE UNINTERRUPTED, TIMELY, SECURE, OR ERROR-FREE; (iii) THE RESULTS THAT MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE USE OF THE SITE,
SERVICES OR MATERIALS WILL BE EFFECTIVE, ACCURATE, OR RELIABLE; (iv) THE QUALITY OF THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OR MATERIALS
PURCHASED OR ACCESSIBLE BY YOU WILL MEET YOUR EXPECTATIONS; AND (v) ANY ERRORS OR DEFECTS IN THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS
WILL BE CORRECTED.
THIS SITE, SERVICES AND MATERIALS MAY INCLUDE TECHNICAL OR OTHER MISTAKES, INACCURACIES, OR TYPOGRAPHICAL ERRORS. BELLEVUE
UNIVERSITY MAY MAKE CHANGES TO THE SITE, MATERIALS AND SERVICES AT ANY TIME IN ITS SOLE DISCRETION AND WITHOUT NOTICE. THE
SITE, MATERIALS AND SERVICES MAY BE OUT OF DATE, AND BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY MAKES NO COMMITMENT TO UPDATE THE SITE, MATERIALS
AND SERVICES.
YOU ACKNOWLEDGE AND AGREE THAT: (i) BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY DOES NOT CONTROL, ENDORSE, OR ACCEPT RESPONSIBILITY FOR ANY MATERIALS
OR SERVICES OFFERED BY THIRD PARTIES AND THIRD PARTIES ACCESSIBLE THROUGH LINKED SITES; (ii) BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY MAKES NO
REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES WHATSOEVER ABOUT ANY SUCH THIRD PARTIES, THEIR MATERIALS OR SERVICES; (iii) ANY DEALINGS YOU MAY
HAVE WITH SUCH THIRD PARTIES ARE AT YOUR OWN RISK; AND (iv) BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY SHALL NOT BE LIABLE OR RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY
MATERIALS OR SERVICES OFFERED BY THIRD PARTIES.
BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY SPECIFICALLY DISCLAIMS ANY LIABILITY WITH REGARD TO THE SITE, SERVICES AND ANY ACTIONS RESULTING FROM YOUR
USE OF THE SITE AND MATERIALS. TO THE MAXIMUM EXTENT PERMITTED BY LAW, BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY WILL HAVE NO LIABILITY RELATED TO
SUBMITTED MATERIALS ARISING UNDER INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY RIGHTS, LIBEL, PRIVACY, PUBLICITY, OBSCENITY OR OTHER LAWS. BELLEVUE
UNIVERSITY ALSO DISCLAIMS ALL LIABILITY WITH RESPECT TO THE MISUSE, LOSS, MODIFICATION OR UNAVAILABILITY OF ANY SUBMITTED
MATERIALS.
THE USE OF THE SITE, SERVICES OR THE DOWNLOADING OR OTHER USE OF ANY MATERIALS IS DONE AT YOUR OWN DISCRETION AND RISK AND
WITH YOUR AGREEMENT THAT YOU WILL BE SOLELY RESPONSIBLE FOR ANY DAMAGE TO YOUR COMPUTER SYSTEM, LOSS OF DATA OR OTHER HARM
THAT RESULTS FROM SUCH ACTIVITIES. BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY ASSUMES NO LIABILITY FOR ANY COMPUTER VIRUS OR OTHER SIMILAR SOFTWARE
CODE THAT IS DOWNLOADED TO YOUR COMPUTER FROM THE SITE OR IN CONNECTION WITH ANY SERVICES OR MATERIALS. NO ADVICE OR
INFORMATION, WHETHER ORAL OR WRITTEN, OBTAINED BY YOU FROM BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY OR VIA THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS SHALL
CREATE ANY WARRANTY NOT EXPRESSLY STATED IN THE TERMS OF USE. BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY WILL NOT BE LIABLE FOR ANY LOSS THAT YOU MAY
INCUR AS A RESULT OF SOMEONE ELSE USING YOUR PASSWORD OR STUDENT ACCOUNT WITH RESPECT TO THE SITE OR ANY SERVICES OR MATERIALS,
EITHER WITH OR WITHOUT YOUR KNOWLEDGE.
SOME STATES OR JURISDICTIONS DO NOT ALLOW THE EXCLUSION OF IMPLIED WARRANTIES OR LIMITATIONS ON HOW LONG AN IMPLIED WARRANTY
MAY LAST, SO THE ABOVE LIMITATIONS MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU. TO THE EXTENT PERMISSIBLE, ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES ARE LIMITED TO
NINETY (90) DAYS.
International Users
This Site can be accessed from countries around the world and may contain references to Bellevue University services and
programs that are not available in your country. These references do not imply that Bellevue University intends to announce
such services or programs in your country. The Site is controlled, operated and administered by Bellevue University from the
United States of America. Bellevue University makes no representation that the Site, the Services or Materials are appropriate
or available for use at other locations outside the United States, and access to the Site from territories where the Site, the
Services or Materials are illegal is prohibited. If you access the Site from a location outside the United States, you are
responsible for compliance with all local laws and United States export control laws, to the extent applicable.
Personal Information and Privacy
Bellevue University will use and protect your Personal Information in accordance with the Bellevue University Website Privacy
Policy available on the Site, the contents of which are incorporated by reference into the Terms of Use.
Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT SHALL BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY ITS AFFILIATES OR THEIR RESPECTIVE OFFICERS, DIRECTORS, PARTNERS, EMPLOYEES, OR AGENTS
BE LIABLE TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY SPECIAL, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, INDIRECT OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES OR LOSSES OF ANY
KIND, OR ANY DAMAGES OR LOSSES WHATSOEVER, INCLUDING THOSE RESULTING FROM LOSS OF USE, DATA OR PROFITS, WHETHER OR NOT
FORESEEABLE OR IF BELLEVUE UNIVERSITY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES OR LOSSES, AND ON ANY THEORY OF
LIABILITY, INCLUDING BREACH OF CONTRACT OR WARRANTY, NEGLIGENCE OR OTHER TORTIOUS ACTION, OR ANY OTHER CLAIM ARISING OUT OF
OR IN CONNECTION WITH: (i) THE ACCESS OR USE OF OR THE INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE THE SITE, SERVICES, OR MATERIALS; (ii) THE
STATEMENTS OR ACTIONS OF ANY THIRD PARTY ON OR VIA THE SITE, SERVICES OR MATERIALS; (iii) ANY DEALINGS WITH VENDORS OR OTHER
THIRD PARTIES; (iv) ANY UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO OR ALTERATION OF YOUR TRANSMISSIONS, USER MATERIALS OR OTHER DATA; (v) ANY
INFORMATION THAT IS SENT OR RECEIVED OR NOT SENT OR RECEIVED; (vi) ANY FAILURE TO STORE OR LOSS OF DATA, FILES, MATERIALS OR
OTHER CONTENT; (vii) ANY SERVICES AVAILABLE THAT ARE DELAYED OR INTERRUPTED; (viii) ANY WEB SITE REFERENCED OR LINKED TO FROM
THIS SITE; OR (ix) YOUR ACCESS TO OR USE OF OR INABILITY TO ACCESS OR USE ANY LINKED SITE. SOME JURISDICTIONS PROHIBIT THE
EXCLUSION OR LIMITATION OF LIABILITY FOR CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES. ACCORDINGLY, THE LIMITATIONS AND EXCLUSIONS SET
FORTH ABOVE MAY NOT APPLY TO YOU.
Spam Email and Postings
In the event of your or others’ access to or use of the Site, Services or Materials in connection with the transmission of
spam newsgroup postings or unsolicited e-mail in violation of these Terms of Use, you acknowledge and agree that Bellevue
University would be irreparably harmed thereunder and that monetary damages would be an insufficient and ineffective remedy;
therefore you agree that Bellevue University is entitled to obtain immediate injunctive relief against any such transmission
(in addition to all other remedies available at law or in equity). Bellevue University may without restriction block, filter
or delete unsolicited e-mail.
SMS Terms and Conditions
Bellevue University’s text messaging service gives you the option to subscribe to receive text messages on your mobile device.
SMS messaging will be used to provide information on upcoming events and announcements (maximum 5 messages per month; msg&data rates may apply), as well as important admission and student servicing reminders.
Subscribing to this service is not required to apply for or gain admission to Bellevue University, and is used only for matters that Bellevue University deems helpful and pertinent.
All mobile information you share will remain confidential and will only be used by Bellevue University representatives to assist you in a more efficient manner regarding the admission process and student servicing.
Bellevue University does not share phone numbers with external sources.
For additional information please refer to Consumer Information at http://www.bellevue.edu/student-support/consumer-information/consumer-information.
All costs associated with receiving a text message are the responsibility of the individual receiving the message.
Receiving mobile text messages from Bellevue University is completely free of charge.
However, message and data rates may apply from your wireless carrier. Carriers are not liable for delayed or undelivered messages.
List of tier 1 carriers include:
T-Mobile
Verizon
AT&T
Sprint
Metro PCS
All users may opt out or unsubscribe from receiving text messages from Bellevue at any time by texting STOP to 76480 or by contacting Bellevue University at 800-756-7920. If you elect to opt out, you will no longer receive text messages from Bellevue University unless you were to re-subscribe to such services.
For help text keyword HELP to 76480 or contact Bellevue University at 1.402.557.7920.
Indemnity and Liability
You agree to indemnify and hold Bellevue University and its affiliates’ and their respective officers, directors, partners,
employees, or agents harmless from any claim or demand, including reasonable attorneys' fees, made by any third party due to
or arising out of: (i) Materials and any other content (e.g. computer viruses) that you may submit, post to or transmit
through the Site (including a third party’s use of such Materials or content (e.g. reliance on the accuracy, completeness or
usefulness of such Materials)); (ii) your access to or use of the Site, Services or Materials; (iii) your connection to the
Site, Services or Materials; (iv) your violation of the Terms of Use; (v) your infringement of any third party’s Intellectual
Property Rights when using or accessing the Site or Services; (vi) your violation of any rights of any third party; or (vii)
your access to or use of Linked Sites and your connections thereto.
Governing Law and Jurisdiction
This Site (excluding Linked Sites) is controlled by Bellevue University from the State of Nebraska. By accessing this Site,
you agree that all matters relating to your access to, or use of, this Site shall be governed by the statutes and laws of the
State of Nebraska, without regard to the conflicts of laws principles thereof. You also agree and hereby submit to the
exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of an appropriate state or federal court in Nebraska with respect to such matters.
General
The Terms of Use and other rules, guidelines, and disclaimers posted via the Site or in connection with the Materials and
Services constitute the entire agreement between Bellevue University and you with respect to your access to or use of the Site,
Materials and Services superseding any prior agreements between you and Bellevue University on such subject matter (including
any prior versions of the Terms of Use). Notwithstanding the foregoing, you expressly acknowledge that your obligations and
responsibilities under the Bellevue University Policies, as applicable, are not superseded by the Terms of Use and that the
Bellevue University Policies shall be used together with the Terms of Use to further the purpose of the Terms of Use to the
fullest extent allowed by law. If for any reason a court of competent jurisdiction finds any provision of the Terms of Use, or
portion thereof, to be unenforceable, that provision shall be enforced to the maximum extent permissible so as to effect the
intent of the parties as reflected by that provision, and the remainder of the Terms of Use shall continue in full force and
effect. Any failure by Bellevue University to enforce or exercise any provision of the Terms of Use or related right shall not
constitute a waiver of that right or provision. The section titles used in the Terms of Use are purely for convenience and
carry with them no legal or contractual effect.
